https://uufsd.org/website-privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
Search for:
Solana Beach, CA 92075
See Map and Directions...
Other Contact Info
Mailing Address:
P.O. Box 201
Solana Beach, CA 92075
Phone: 858-755-9225
Email: office@uufsd.org
Like Us on Facebook...
Follow Us on Twitter...
Website Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by the Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of San Dieguito (UUFSD), referred to in this policy as “we”. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This privacy policy addresses those concerns. This policy may be changed or updated from time to time.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at office@uufsd.org.
We are available to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
The first principle of Unitarian Universalism is to covenant to affirm and promote the inherent worth and dignity of every person. We believe that this principle impels us to protect the privacy of visitors.
Personal Information
Our site collects personal information from our visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, address, phone number, email address, credit card numbers, and similar information. We do not require this information to obtain access to any part of our site. We do not sell or rent this personal information to other organizations.
The personal information we collect is only used by us to process a request that has been placed by the visitor. We never sell your email address and if you voluntarily give it to us, we will strive to use it only for what it was intended. If we pass it, it would only be to the congregation or person who has the information you desire.
Statistical Information Collected
We collect information on the browsing habits of users and the companies that provide that service also have access to that information. This site collects information using cookies and javascript, so if they are enabled in your browser, information can be collected, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and country. This information is only used for statistical purposes and cannot identify you as an individual.
Information Accuracy
We make reasonable effort to ensure that the information presented is correct and accurate. If inaccuracies occur, we will make reasonable effort to correct them in a timely manner. To report any web site inaccuracies or for questions about our Privacy Policy please email us at office@uufsd.org.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our web sites contain some hyperlinks to web sites operated by parties other than us. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such web sites and are not responsible for their contents or privacy policies. The inclusion of hyperlinks to other web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on these web sites or any association with their operators.
Section Navigation
Upcoming EventsNo events
News & Announcements
Monthly Call To Action – December
GENEROSITY SUNDAY FOR GENTE UNIDA – SUNDAY, NOVEMBER 22, 2020
UUFSD Email alias list published
Drive through CDC food drive
Monthly Call to Action – November
Generosity Sunday Oct 25th is for Camp de Benneville Pines.
Happy News—Our Endowment is Activated!
Music Notes
Archives Archives
Select Month
December 2020  (1)
November 2020  (2)
October 2020  (6)
September 2020  (7)
August 2020  (7)
July 2020  (6)
June 2020  (11)
May 2020  (7)
April 2020  (9)
March 2020  (8)
February 2020  (15)
January 2020  (5)
December 2019  (8)
November 2019  (7)
October 2019  (6)
September 2019  (10)
August 2019  (16)
July 2019  (8)
June 2019  (16)
May 2019  (8)
April 2019  (25)
March 2019  (9)
February 2019  (11)
January 2019  (19)
December 2018  (8)
November 2018  (21)
October 2018  (17)
September 2018  (23)
August 2018  (18)
July 2018  (16)
June 2018  (17)
May 2018  (33)
April 2018  (17)
March 2018  (10)
